A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Museology, 1962-2006; 15; 23.55 Cubic Feet 62 letter document boxes
  - Japan, 15.9
    - Etoh, Shun, B-6531, DF-6641, 1966 (Box 677, Folder 3)
    - Kelman, Donald, NYU, B-6887, B-6983, B-70105, B-7148, 1968-1971 (Box 677, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Tsujimoto, Kanya, DF-7441, 1974 (Box 677, Folder 5)
    - Yamamoto, Chikyo, B-6934, 1969 (Box 677, Folder 6)
    - Yashiro, Yukio, DF-6605, 1966 (Box 677, Folder 7)
    - Koyano (formerly Saito), Masako, B-6428, B-6524, B-6719, DF-6778, DF-6841, 1964-1968 (Box 635, Folder 1)
    - Fiske, Betty, EC-8566(30)R, 1985 (Box 677, Folder 8)
    - Hopkins, Henry, B-8580(30)R, 1985 (Box 677, Folder 9)
    - Moriya, Takeshi, B-8434(30)R, 1984 (Box 677, Folder 10)
    - Nakazawa, B-8586(30)R, 1985 (Box 677, Folder 11)
    - Museology-Japan, Boulton, Ann, B-8871(30)R, 1988 (Box 678, Folder 1)
    - Museology-Japan, Dawn, Antoinette, EC-8710(30)R, 1987 (Box 678, Folder 2)
    - Museology-Japan, Felker, Csilla, EC-8891(30)R, 1988 (Box 678, Folder 3)
    - Museology-Japan, Hori, Akira, B-86101(30)R, 1986 (Box 678, Folder 4)
    - Museology-Japan, Mitsuyama, Kiyoko, EC-8609(30)R, 1986 (Box 678, Folder 5)
    - Museology-Japan, Takashina, Shuji, B-6757, EC-7483, 1967; 1974 (Box 678, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Douglas, EC-8709(30), 1987 (Box 678, Folder 7)
    - Moes, Robert, B-8699(30)R, 1986 (Box 678, Folder 8)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art, B-8974(30), 1989 (Box 678, Folder 9)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Springfield, Massachusetts, B-90106(30), 1990 (Box 678, Folder 10)
    - Nishio, Yoshiyuki, B-7619, B-7722, 1976-1977 (Box 679, Folder 1)
    - Reynolds, Valrae, B-8962(56), 1989 (Box 679, Folder 2)
    - Sogetsu Museum, B-8530(30)R, 1985 (Box 679, Folder 3)
    - Tucker, Marcia, B-8973 (30), 1989 (Box 679, Folder 4)
    - Beal, Graham, B-8763(30)R, 1987 (Box 679, Folder 5)
    - Grimes, John, B-8761(30)R, 1987 (Box 680, Folder 1)
    - Yabe, Yoshiaki, DF-9170, 1991 (Box 680, Folder 2)
    - Contemporary Arts Museum, 704-00-97013-203.2, 1997 (Box 680, Folder 3)
    - Constantine, Mildred, B-8428(30)R, 1984 (Box 680, Folder 4)
    - Harvard University Art Museums, JUMP, 704-00-97014-203.2, 1997 (Box 680, Folder 5)
    - Harvard University Art Museums, JUMP, 704-00-98089-203.1 (Box 711, Folder 1)
    - Hasegawa, Yuko, B-9144(251), 1991 (Box 680, Folder 6)
    - Igarashi, Masaru, DF-9172, 1991 (Box 680, Folder 7)
    - Kline, Katy, DF-9223, 1992 (Box 680, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, B-9284(30), 1992 (Box 681, Folder 1)
    - Koyano, Mika, 7004-00-96073-203.000-1, 1989-1992 (Box 681, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, JUMP Program, 704-00-97015-203.2, 1997 (Box 681, Folder 3)
    - Mattress Factory, JUMP Program, 704-00-97016-203.2, 1997 (Box 681, Folder 4)
    - Museum of Modern Art, JUMP Program, 704-00-97017-203.3, 1997 (Box 681, Folder 5)
    - Peabody Essex Museum, 704-00-97101-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 681, Folder 6)
    - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, JUMP Program, 704-00-97018-203.2, 1997 (Box 681, Folder 7)
    - Sano, Emily, B-9156(30), 1991 (Box 681, Folder 8)
    - Stinchecum, Amanda, B-8537(30)R, 1985 (Box 681, Folder 9)
    - Trippi, Laura, B-9282(330), B-9281(30), 1992 (Box 681, Folder 10)
    - Walker Art Center, JUMP Program, 704-00-97019-203.2, 1997 (Box 681, Folder 11)
    - Friedman, Martin, 704-00-95080-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 682, Folder 1)
    - Goncharov, Kathleen, 704-00-98084-203.1, 1998 (Box 682, Folder 2)
    - Kimura, Yuko, 3739-604191-41001 (Box 682, Folder 3)
    - List Visual Arts Center-MIT, JUMP, 704-00-20107-203.1, 2000 (Box 682, Folder 4)
    - Ota, Yasuto, 607-00-20036-203.4, 2000 (Box 682, Folder 5)
    - Suzuki, Jun, 100-00-21047-203.3, 2001 (Box 683, Folder 1)
    - Walker Art Center, 704-00-98091-203.1, 1998 (Box 683, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Jane, 704-00-21113-203.1, 2001 (Box 683, Folder 3)
    - Hasegawa, Yuko, 704-00-21032-203.2, 2001 (Box 683, Folder 4-5)
    - Kumagai, Isako, 710-00-22110-203.1, 2002 (Box 684, Folder 1)
    - Matake, Makiko, JUMP Program (Box 684, Folder 2)
    - Yamacuchi, Yozo, JUMP Program, 100-00-22039-203.3, 2002 (Box 684, Folder 3)
    - Torii, Izumi, 593-00-99124-203.4, 1999 (Box 684, Folder 4)
    - Rose, Bernice, B-8581(30)R, 1985 (Box 684, Folder 5)
    - Kwon, Yigu, Museo-Korea, 1976 (Box 685, Folder 1)
    - Kim, Che-Won, DF-6522, 1965 (Box 685, Folder 2)
    - Kwon, Yigu, University of Pennsylvania, B-7318, B-7316, B-7421, B-7523, B-7727, 1973-1977 (Box 685, Folder 3)
    - Lee, Youngja, New York University (NYU), EC-6904, B-7042, 1969-1970 (Box 685, Folder 4)
    - National Folklore Museum of Korea, Rhie, Jong-Chul (Box 685, Folder 5)
    - National Folklore Museum of Korea, Museo-Korea, B-7459, EC-7764, (RHIE), 1974-1977 (Box 686, Folder 1)
    - Painting and Sculpture-Korea, Kim, Tchah Sup, B-7522, B-7620, 1975-1976 (Box 686, Folder 2)
    - Museology-Korea, Rathbun, William, B-8741955)R, 1987 (Box 686, Folder 3)
    - Kim, Kumja, B-90999(314), 1990 (Box 686, Folder 4)
    - Cunningham, Michael, B9-8740(55)R Canceled, B-9333(314), 1993 (Box 686, Folder 5)
    - Kang, Woo-Bang, B-8440(26), R-8312(7), R-8223(7), 1982-1984 (Box 686, Folder 6)
    - Lee, Insook, B-9123, 1991 (Box 687, Folder 1)
    - Kyonggi Provincial Museum, 100-00-98116-203.3, 1998 (Box 687, Folder 2)
    - Jang, Kyung Hwa, 100-00-20156-203.1, 2000 (Box 687, Folder 3)
  - Laos, 15.10
    - Baskin, Bonnie, 100-00-99053-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 687, Folder 4)
    - Keopannha, Vanpheng, 634-00-23086-203.1, 100-00-21018-203.2, 2001-2003 (Box 687, Folder 5)
    - Nhilatchay, Sisavath, 634-00-21159-203.1, 2001 (Box 687, Folder 6)
  - Malaysia, 15.11
    - Zain, Ismail, Museo-Malaysia, B-7458, 1974 (Box 688, Folder 1)
    - McCredie, Davis William, DF-7842, 1978 (Box 688, Folder 2)
    - National Art Gallery, Kuala Lumpur, Ismail Bin Zain, B-7458-MCR, 1974 (Box 688, Folder 3)
    - Kalb, Laurie Beth, 706-00-98075-203.1, 1998 (Box 688, Folder 4)
    - Museology-Malasyia, Tee, Janet Siew Mooi, 702-00-20075-203.1, 2000 (Box 688, Folder 5)
  - Mongolia, 15.12
    - Asian Art Museum of San Francisco, 702-00-94043-203.000-1, EC-9207(314), 1994 (Box 688, Folder 6)
    - Balboa Art Conservation Center, Teresa Heady, 706-00-21098-203.1, 2001 (Box 689, Folder 1)
    - Northeast Document Conservation Center, 706-00-21100-203.1, 2001 (Box 689, Folder 2)
    - Northeast Document Conservation Center, 706-00-20089-203.1, 2000 (Box 689, Folder 3)
    - Asian Art of San Francisco, 100-00-210410-203.4, 2001 (Box 689, Folder 4)
    - Asian Art of San Francisco, 100-00-98034-203.4, 517-00-97050-203.1, 1998 (Box 689, Folder 5)
    - Fischer, Hal, 100-00-21073-203.1, 2001 (Box 689, Folder 6)
  - Nepal, 15.13
    - Nepalese Conservation Students, Mishra, Tarananda, B-7063, 1970 (Box 689, Folder 7)
  - Pakistan, 15.14
    - Dar, Saifur Tahman, B-7829, 1978 (Box 690, Folder 1)
    - Lahore Museum, B-7171-MCR, 1971 (Box 690, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Folk Heritage, Mufti, Uxi (Box 691, Folder 1)
    - Institute of Folk Heritage, B-7461-MCR, 1974 (Box 690, Folder 3)
    - Dar, Saifur Rahman, B-7829, 1978 (Box 690, Folder 4)
    - National Museum, Pakistan, R-8230(7), 1982 (Box 690, Folder 5)
  - Philippines, 15.15
    - Casino, Eric, DF-7475, 1974 (Box 691, Folder 2)
    - Chabet, Roberto, Institute of International Educaiton (IIE), B-6837, DF-68102, 1968 (Box 691, Folder 3)
    - Baradas, David, B-7538, 1975 (Box 691, Folder 4)
    - Escultura, Noel, B-8017, 1980 (Box 691, Folder 5)
    - Villaluz, Gerry, 702-00-99016-203.2, 1999 (Box 691, Folder 6)
    - Capistrano-Baker, Florina, 100-00-25147-203.3, 2005 (Box 692, Folder 1)
    - National Museum, Philppines, 100-00-25150-203.3, 2005 (Box 692, Folder 2)
  - Sikkim, 15.16
    - Densapa, Tashi T., B-7529, DF-7551, DF-7562, 1975 (Box 692, Folder 3)
  - Singapore, 15.17
    - Museology-Singapore, Ballard, Mary, B-8850(55)R, 1988 (Box 692, Folder 4)
    - Lim, Chong Quek, DF-7564, DF-7671, B-7602, DF7570, B-7625, 1975-1976 (Box 692, Folder 5)
    - Ng-Lim, chong Quek, B-8938, 1989 (Box 692, Folder 6)
  - Sri Lanka, 15.18
    - P. H. D. H. de Silva, Institute of International Education (IIE), 1970 (Box 693, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan, 15.19
    - Yuan, Jai, B-70111-MCR, 1970 (Box 693, Folder 2)
    - Chang Mei, Lin-Sheng, B-7325, B-7409, 1973-1974 (Box 693, Folder 3)
    - Chang, Shih-Hsien, NYU Conservancy Center, B-7326, 1973 (Box 693, Folder 4)
    - Wang, Richard Ch'iu T'u, University of Michigan, B-7223, 1972 (Box 693, Folder 5)
  - Thailand, 15.20
    - National Museum, Bangkok, Book Contribution, Chira Chongkol, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 693, Folder 6)
    - National Museum, Bangkok, B-7460-MCR, 1974 (Box 693, Folder 7)
    - Bangkok National Museum Curators, Chingkol and Ek, B-6838, B-7142, 1968; 1971 (Box 694, Folder 1)
    - Khantharo, Methee, National Museum, Bangkok, B-7172-MCR, 1971 (Box 694, Folder 2)
    - Siam Society, B-6511, 1965 (Box 694, Folder 3)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project, National Museum, Bangkok 1973, B-73101-MCR, B-7464-MCR, 1974 (Box 694, Folder 4)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project, National Museum, Bangkok, B-73101-MCR, B-7464-MCR, 1973 December-1974 May (Box 694, Folder 5)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project, National Museum, Bangkok, B-73101-MCR, B-7464-MCR, 1974 (Box 694, Folder 6)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project, National Museum, Bangkok, B-73101-MCR, B-7464-MCR, 1974 December-1975 April 30 (Box 695, Folder 1)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project, National Museum, Bangkok, B-73101-MCR, B-7464-MCR, 1975 May 1 (Box 695, Folder 2)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project, Project Proposals: Drafts and Final Version, B-73101-MCR, 1973-1974 (Box 695, Folder 3)
    - Phongprayoon, Chunphunut, B-7679, B-7782, 1976-1977 (Box 696, Folder 1)
    - Rajpatik, Waranghana, B-7736, B-7833, B-7929, B-8019, 1977-1980 (Box 696, Folder 2)
    - Siam Society, B-7640-AIP, 1976 (Box 696, Folder 3)
    - Rajpitak, Warangkhana, Institute of Archaeology, 1979 (Box 696, Folder 4)
    - Thai Bronze Conservation Project (Box 943, Folder 4)
    - Siam Society (Box 941, Folder 4)
    - Bangkok National Museum Curators, Chongkol and Ek, B-6838, B-7142, 1968-1971 (Box 697, Folder 1)
    - Museology-Thailand, Hock, Nancy, B-8851(55)R, 1988 (Box 697, Folder 2)
    - Museology-Thailand, Smith, Rika, B-8742(55)R, 1987 (Box 697, Folder 3)
    - Rajpitak, Warangkhana, B-8043, R-8220(4), B-8116(4), 1980-1982 (Box 697, Folder 4)
    - SPAFA, DF-88122, 1988 (Box 697, Folder 5)
    - Strahan, Donna,B-9245(314), 1992 (Box 697, Folder 6)
    - Woodward, Hiram, Jr., B-9246(314), 1992 (Box 698, Folder 1)
    - Posithong, Prapassorn, 634-00-22116-203.1, 2002 (Box 698, Folder 2)
    - Atimana, Uthit, 634-00-23025-203.2, 2003 (Box 698, Folder 3-4)
  - Vietnam, 15.21
    - American Museum of Natural History, B-9335(314), 1993 (Box 698, Folder 5)
    - Aid to Artisans, 100-00-22155-203.3, 2002 (Box 699, Folder 1)
    - University of California, Fowler Museum, 702-00-20077-203.1, 2000 (Box 699, Folder 2)
    - American Museum of Natural History, 2000-2006 (Box 699, Folder 3)
    - Proschan, Frank, 517-00-97053-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 699, Folder 4)
    - Dao, Tran Thi Thanh, 634-00-21160-203.1, 2001 (Box 699, Folder 5)
    - Hoa, Trinh Thi, 634-00-21161-203.1, 2001 (Box 699, Folder 6)
    - Vietnam Museum of Ethnology, 100-00-99051-203.1, 1999 (Box 700, Folder 1)
    - Vietnam Musuem of Ethnology, 100-00-20035-203.3, 2000 (Box 700, Folder 2)
    - Huy, Nguyen Wan, 705-00-99144-203.1, 1999 (Box 700, Folder 3)
  - West Irian, 15.22
    West New Guinea (Indonesia)
    - Chatib, Daniel, Museo-West Irian, B-71107MCR, 1971 (Box 700, Folder 4)
    - Korwa, Arie Jan, Tienderwasih University, B-71107-MCR-1, 1971 (Box 700, Folder 5)
    - Cenderwasih University, Institute of Anthropology, Supplies-Equipment, B-71107-MCR-2, 1971 (Box 701, Folder 1)
    - Chatib, Daniel, Tienderwasih University, Library, B-71107-MCR-3, B-73100, 1971-1973 (Box 701, Folder 2)
    - Iskandar, Anwas, Cenderawasih University, Institute of Anthropology, B-71107-MCR, 1971 (Box 701, Folder 3)
    - Asmat Museum of Culture and Progress, Project Related Material, B-7273-MCR, 1972 (Box 701, Folder 4)
- Music, 1963-2006; 16; 30.94 Cubic Feet 79 letter document boxes and 1 record storage box
  - Afghanistan, 16.1
    - Smithsonian Folkways Recordings (Box 701, Folder 5)
  - Asia, 16.2
    - Heins, Ernst, Society for Ethnomusicology, Ann Arbor, DF-7071, 1969 November 13-16 (Box 701, Folder 6)
    - National Music Council, International Music Council Assembly and Congress, Sixth International Congress, Twelfth General Assembly of the International Music Council, B-6869, 1968 September (Box 701, Folder 7)
    - Julliard School of Music, B-6715, B-6771, B-6810, B-6924, 1967-1969 (Box 701, Folder 8)
    - Julliard School of Music, B-6715, 1967 (Box 702, Folder 1)
    - Curtis Institute of Music Fellowships, B-7503, 1975 (Box 702, Folder 2)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, New and Newer Music Series, DF-7392, 1973 (Box 702, Folder 3)
    - Marlboro School of Music, Mari Tsumura, B-70102, 1970 (Box 702, Folder 4)
    - National Guild Community Music Schools, Music Teacher Project-Korea-Taiwan, Oboe: Othello Jerol Clark and Bassoon: James D. Hough, Jr., B-7108, B-7232, B-7303, 1971-1973 (Box 702, Folder 5)
    - University of Washington, Garfias, Robert, B-6623, B-6781, DF-6788, 1966-1967 (Box 702, Folder 6)
    - Wesleyan University, World Music Program, Asian Artist in Residence, B-7109, B-7229, B-7302, B-7403, 1971-1974 (Box 702, Folder 7)
    - Wesleyan University, 3 Visiting Artists, Araki, Kodo, Robertus Soedarsono, Benedictus Suharto, B-7066, 1970 (Box 702, Folder 8)
    - Zipper, Herbert, Travel Study, DF-69104, B-70106, DF-7199, DF-7289, DF-7398, 1969-1973 (Box 702, Folder 9)
    - American Musicological Society, Twelfth Congress of International Music Society, B-7740, 1977 (Box 703, Folder 1)
    - Asian Composers? League-5th Annual Conference, EC-7872, DF-7876, 1978 (Box 703, Folder 2)
    - University of Washington, School of Music, B-7601, B-7701, 1976-1977 (Box 703, Folder 3)
    - Brown University, B-7501, EC-7632, 1975-1976 (Box 703, Folder 4)
    - WNCN FM Radio, Chou, Wen-Chung, B-7164, DF-7385, 1971 (Box 703, Folder 5)
    - Asian Composer?s League-5th Annual Conference, EC-7872, 1978 (Box 704, Folder 1)
    - Ambassadors of Opera, DF-8543(42)R, 1985 (Box 704, Folder 2)
    - Hatch, Martin F., B-8752(56)R, 1987 (Box 704, Folder 3)
    - International Council of Music, B-8842, 1988 (Box 704, Folder 4)
    - University of California, San Diego, Pacific Ring, EC-8605, 1986 (Box 704, Folder 5)
    - World Music Institute, DF-88124, 1988 (Box 704, Folder 6)
    - Asian Composers League, 706-00-96071-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 704, Folder 7)
    - Monk, Meredith-The House, 100-00-97001-203.000-3, 1997 (Box 704, Folder 8)
    - World Music Institute, 100-00-95128-203.000-3, DF-92107, DF-9193, 1991-1995 (Box 705, Folder 1)
    - Livingston, Hugh, 100-00-21004-203.3, 2001 (Box 705, Folder 2)
    - Lincoln Center Festival, 100-00-22132-203.1, 2002 (Box 705, Folder 3)
    - Ung, Chinary, 100-00-21003-203.3, 2001 (Box 705, Folder 4)
    - Uno, Yayoi, 706-00-990707-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 705, Folder 5)
    - American Musicological Society, Interdisciplinary Horizons in the Study of Musical Traditions East and West, The Twelfth Congress of the International Musicological Society, Berkeley, CA, 1977 (Box 947)
    - International Musicological Society, Report of the Twelfth Congress, Berkeley, 1977 (Box 947)
  - Burma, 16.3
    - Keeler, Ward William, 706-00-96012-203.000-2, 1996 (Box 705, Folder 6)
    - Keeler, Ward, and Rick Heizman, 706-00-99071-203.1, 1999 (Box 705, Folder 7)
    - Ko Ko, U, B-9249(26), 1992 (Box 705, Folder 8)
    - Keeler, Ward, 706-00-24069-203.1, 2004 (Box 705, Folder 9)
    - Asia Society, 702-00-23012-203.2, 2003 (Box 705, Folder 10)
  - Cambodia, 16.4
    - Ung, Chinary, Columbia University, B-7027, B-7098, B-7204, EC-7112, B-7307, B-7408, 1970-1974 (Box 706, Folder 1)
    - Sam, Ang-Sam, Dissertation, The Pin Peat Ensemble, Volume 1 and 2, 1988 (Box 706, Folder 2-3)
    - Sam, Sam-Ang, B-8510, B-8617, B-8310(7), B-8436(26)R, 1983-1985 (Box 707, Folder 1-2)
    - Sam, Sam-Ang, 100-00-23119-203.3, 2003 (Box 707, Folder 3)
    - Sam, Sam-Ang, 100-00-99015-203.2, 100-00-99141-203.1, 1999 (Box 707, Folder 4)
    - Sam, Sam-Ang, 194-00-96116-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 708, Folder 1)
    - Southwest Chamber Music, 718-00-24020-203.2, 2004 (Box 708, Folder 2)
    - Him, Sophy, 100-00-21054-203.1, 2001 (Box 708, Folder 3)
    - Khmer Culture Association, 718-00-24095-203.1, 2004 (Box 708, Folder 4)
    - Ung, Chinary and Susan, 100-00-22064-203.1, 2002 (Box 708, Folder 5)
  - China, 16.5
    - Pian, (Mrs.) Rulan Chao, B-6620, 1966 (Box 708, Folder 6)
    - Langlitz, Davis, DF-8505, 1985 (Box 708, Folder 7)
    - Shanghai Music Project, R-8210(14), DF-8211, 1982 (Box 709, Folder 1)
    - University of Maryland Baltimore County, B-8521, 1985 (Box 709, Folder 2)
    - Xiao, Hong-Mei, B-8420, B-8513, 1984-1985 (Box 709, Folder 3)
    - Center for US-China Arts Exchange, R-8315(7), 1983 (Box 709, Folder 4)
    - Center for US-China Arts Exchange, Contemporary Music Concert, DF-8136, 1981 (Box 709, Folder 5)
    - Center for US-China Arts Exchange, Delay, Dorothy, DF-8129, 1981 (Box 709, Folder 6)
    - Hough, James D., DF-8702, 1987 (Box 709, Folder 7)
    - Ni, Wen-Zhen, B-8571, DF-8970, 1985-1989 (Box 709, Folder 8)
    - Yang, Dajing, DF-8703, B-8620, 1986-1987 (Box 709, Folder 9)
    - Center for US-China Arts Exchange, DF-8880, 1988 (Box 709, Folder 10)
    - Chen, Xieyang, B-8117, DF-8138, 1981 (Box 710, Folder 1)
    - Chou, Wen Chung, B-9080(29), DF-7845, DF-7864, 1978-1990 (Box 710, Folder 2)
    - Chou, Wen Chung, B-9195(39), 1991 (Box 710, Folder 3)
    - He, Qian-san, EC-9302, 1993 (Box 710, Folder 4)
    - Lee, Byongwong, B-9369(56), 1993 (Box 710, Folder 5)
    - Slobin, Mark, 100-00-97032-203.000-3, 1997 (Box 710, Folder 6)
    - Ynag, Yandi, B-9232, 1992 (Box 710, Folder 7)
    - Bresnick, Martin, 100-00-22137-203.3, 2002 (Box 711, Folder 2)
    - Brown, Emily Freeman, 706-00-97073-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 711, Folder 3)
    - Bryant, Lei, 706-00-22085-203.1, 2002 (Box 711, Folder 4)
    - Hilbish, Thomas, 517-00-97047-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 711, Folder 5)
    - Liu, Yunzhi, 100-00-22038-203.3, 100-00-21056-203.1, 2001-2002 (Box 711, Folder 6)
    - Livingston, Hugh, 100-00-99052-203.1, 1999 (Box 711, Folder 7)
    - Tu, Yu Liang, 653-00-22050-203.4, 632-00-21052-203.4, 2001-2002 (Box 711, Folder 8)
    - Music and Theater Research Library Foundation, 100-00-98001-203.3, 1998 (Box 711, Folder 9)
    - Music for the Earth, 100-00-22037-203.3, 2002 (Box 711, Folder 10)
    - Qu, Xiaosong, B-8834, B-89103, 1988-1989 (Box 712, Folder 1)
    - Silk Road Project, 100-00-20060-203.1, 2000 (Box 712, Folder 2)
    - University of Arkansas, 100-00-20091-203.1, 2000 (Box 712, Folder 3)
    - Yang, Liqing, 451-00-94049-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 712, Folder 4)
    - Wang, Xi-Lin, 100-00-94017-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 713, Folder 1)
    - Zevik, Emma and Sichuan Conservatory of Music, 479-00-96040-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 713, Folder 2)
    - Zhou, Kiamo, 702-00-98053-203.1, 1998 (Box 713, Folder 3)
    - Zou, Xiangping, 100-00-98110-203.3, 1998 (Box 713, Folder 4)
    - Azruni, Sahan, 100-00-99142-203.1, 1999 (Box 713, Folder 5)
    - Fang, Jianjun, 702-00-22072-203.1 (Box 714, Folder 1)
    - Guo, Wenjing, 452-00-95057-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 714, Folder 2)
    - Jia, Daqun, 004-00-25058-203.1, 2005 (Box 714, Folder 3)
    - Lawergren, Bo, 706-00-24070-203.1, 2004 (Box 714, Folder 4)
    - Mao, Jizeng, 702-00-23047-203.1, 2003 (Box 715, Folder 1)
    - Tang, Jianping, 100-00-24064-203.1, 2004 (Box 715, Folder 2)
    - University of Arkansas, 702-00-23054-203.1, 2003 (Box 715, Folder 3)
    - University of California, San Deigo, 100-00-23126-203.3, 2003 (Box 715, Folder 4)
    - Xu, Changjun, 100-00-21050-203.3, 100-00-20041-203.1, 2000-2001 (Box 715, Folder 5)
    - Yeh, Tsung, 100-00-22016-203.2, 2002 (Box 715, Folder 6)
    - Wang, Yanyan, DD-8903(184-186-188-240), DD-8902(182), EC-8404, B-88112, DD-9001(270), DD-9091(311), 1989 (Box 716, Folder 1)
  - Hong Kong, 16.6
    - Chow, Chi Chung, DD-9120(325), 1991 (Box 716, Folder 2)
    - Society for Ethnomusicology Research, B-8863(HK)R, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 3)
    - International Council for Traditional Music, B-9051(HK), 1990 (Box 716, Folder 4)
    - Tsui, Katusha, B-9048(HK), 1990 (Box 716, Folder 5)
    - Wing Ying, Cecilia, DD-9320(399), 1993 (Box 716, Folder 6)
    - Leung, Wai Wa, B-9357(HK), 1993 (Box 717, Folder 1)
    - Lung, Heung-Wing, B-9356(HK), 1993 (Box 717, Folder 2)
    - Tse, Jackson Luen Wah, DD-9226(387), 1992 (Box 717, Folder 3)
    - Wong, Sun Keung, B-93362(401), 1993 (Box 717, Folder 4)
    - Chan, Yan Yan, 468-00-94089-203.000-4, 1994 (Box 717, Folder 5)
    - Chin, Kwok Wai, 332-00-95061-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 717, Folder 6)
    - Law, Wing-fai, 465-00-94054-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 717, Folder 7)
    - Ng, Poly, 332-00-94056-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 718, Folder 1)
    - Tong, Kin-Woon, B-8118, B-8213, 1981-1982 (Box 718, Folder 2)
    - Tong, Shiu Wai, 451-00-94051-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 718, Folder 3)
    - Yang, Ingrid Chang-ying, 452-00-96060-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 718, Folder 4)
    - Chow, Maria Mai Wah, B-9361(401), 1993 (Box 718, Folder 5)
    - Cheung, Florence Pui Chan, 613-00-20083-203.1, 2000 (Box 718, Folder 6)
    - Chou, Oliver Kwong Chung, 624-00-21144-203.4, 2001 (Box 719, Folder 1)
    - Friedenberg, Kenneth, 517-00-97150-1, 1997 (Box 719, Folder 2)
    - Kam, Wing-chong, 564-00-98036-203.4, 1998 (Box 719, Folder 3)
    - Kung, Chi Shing, 452-00-96059-203.000-1, 450-00-94045-203.000-1, 1994-1996 (Box 719, Folder 4-5)
    - Leung, Siu Ying, 647-00-22041-203.4, 2002 (Box 720, Folder 1)
    - Leung, Priscilla. 100-00-20031-203.3, 585-00-99064-203.1, 1999-2000 (Box 720, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 100-00-21009-203.3, 2001 (Box 720, Folder 3)
    - Suen Wan Ting, 631-00-21091-203.1, 2001 (Box 720, Folder 4)
    - Tam, Alex (Tin Lok Tam), 564-00-99034-203.4, 1999 (Box 720, Folder 5)
    - Tsang, Richard, B-9262(HK), 1992 (Box 720, Folder 6)
    - Yip, Stephen Shu-Kin, 478-00-95024-203.000-4, 1995 (Box 720, Folder 7)
    - Yung, Regina, 332-00-94057-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 720, Folder 8)
    - Yap, Man-Shan, 564-00-20039-203.4, 2000 (Box 720, Folder 9)
    - Fung, Ka Hing, 723-00-24035-203.1, 2004 (Box 721, Folder 1)
    - Lam, Kai Yin Crystal, 757-00-25130-203.4, 2005 (Box 721, Folder 2)
    - Lee, John Yin Shing, 652-00-22081-203.1 (Box 721, Folder 3)
    - Li-Kien, Liew, 681-00-23034-203.4, 2003 (Box 721, Folder 4)
    - Loo Jia En, Aenon, 624-00-21051-203.4, 2001 (Box 721, Folder 5)
    - So, Lewis Ting Cheong, B-9285(306), 1995 (Box 721, Folder 6)
    - Siu, Chun Kit Louis, 758-00-25129-203.4, 2005 (Box 721, Folder 7)
    - Tang, Lok Yin, 724-00-24036-203.4, 2004 (Box 721, Folder 8)
    - Yu, Kai Wai, 687-00-23036-203.4, 2003 (Box 721, Folder 9)
  - India, 16.7
    - Becker, Robert, B-7509, 1975 (Box 722, Folder 1)
    - Brinda, T., University of Washington, DF-6969, 1969 (Box 722, Folder 2)
    - Congress for Cultural Freedom, India Conference with M. Hood and R. Gargias, B-6401, 1964-1967 (Box 722, Folder 3)
    - Council for Tibetan Education, DF-7554, 1975 (Box 722, Folder 4)
    - Gonsalves, Anthony Jose, DF-6644, DF-6676, 1966 (Box 722, Folder 5)
    - Dutt, Mohan, DF-6673, 1966 (Box 722, Folder 6)
    - Jairazbhoy, Nazir Ali, DF-6970, 1969 (Box 722, Folder 7)
    - Khursedji, Hilla N., Curtis Institute, B-7206, 1972 (Box 722, Folder 8)
    - Leifer, Lyon, Institute of International Education (IIE), B-6828, 1968 (Box 722, Folder 9)